Well let me wish you, Happy Wonderful Year
Good morning
Viewers all over the world,
Happy Wonderful New Year
I call it a wonderful year because it's a wonderful year.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you
This year is a wonderful year.
I know many nations have not yet entered the new year
but I want to tell you what you are about to enter, or what you have entered
is a wonderful one.
Amen!!!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
And those nations that have a different calendar.
But in all, 2017 is a wonderful year.
Amen!!!
And it's so wonderful for you, people of God.
After going through the whole thing -
the revelation and what we should be expecting in the year -
you will agree with me so wonderful.
I don't know how to call it.
Will i call it new year or new beginning or whatever but I chose the word wonderful.
Because it's so wonderful.
It demands trust and obey.
The year demands trust and obey.
That's why I said it is wonderful: It's a wonderful year because of what it demands.
If you want to go through the year, enjoy the year, overcome and walk through it smoothly,
just trust and obey.
That is why I call it a wonderful year.
This year we will experience challenges and some of these challenges are going to be unique.
When something is unique, there are things that you will not know how to handle
because you have never gone through them before.
There are not things you can handle.
When things you can handle come, you can say, "Yes, let me apply the former tactic,
the strategy I used in the past".
But for the one that is unique, you will say, "Ah, I don't know how to go about this".
A lot of these challenges will be very unique - different from what you know and are used to.
Remember yesterday I told you that no matter the challenges, they will not impair you but improve you -
just trust and obey.
The reason why there will be so many challenges and unique ones is because there is a dream for you.
Today, take my word, you have a dream.
Tell your neighbor: "I have a dream".
A dream is something that you may not know but people can tell you, "You have a dream".
You say what is the dream?
This year will come with so many challenges and unique ones because you have a dream.
There is something the Lord said to me that I should tell you -
the voice of their wailing shall be silenced.
Amen!!
That is - tell your people the voice of their wailing will be silenced.
This means that God is there to intervene and to rescue you.
The outcome of this is a dream - dream of breakthrough - the outcome of challenges.
You have nothing to worry about - just trust and obey
The Lord says, the voice of trouble shall be silenced.
What else again?
The voice of difficulty shall be silenced.
Setback, hardship, just name them, shall be silenced.
It means these will come; you will only hear the crying but they will not reach you.
Amen!!
Voice means strength - their strength, their ability to destroy you, to kill you will be combated.
Just trust and obey
Tell your neighbour, "Just trust and obey".
Those dreams, you thought were lost, they are not lost.
There are a lot of dreams you had in the past and you keep asking yourself -
I dreamt I gave a handshake to this man three years ago but I have never met the man until now.
There are lot of question you keep asking yourself, no one to answer.
Those dreams are not lost.
Amen!!
This year, dream of breakthrough - a new dream for you (Amen!!!)
Write it down, write it down.
I am just giving you the summary of what is here.
Dream of breakthrough (Amen!!) - a new dream for you (Amen).
Just trust and obey.
Amidst trouble, that is in the midst of challenges you will find yourself in.
But the Lord says, "The voice of challenges shall be silenced!" (Amen)
The outcome of the temptation and difficult circumstances you will be going through,
the outcome of unique challenges you will be going through -
dream of breakthrough, a new dream for you.
Amen!!!
Dream of prosperity, a new dream for you.
Are you writing it down?
These are the dreams you were supposed to have yourself but you could not,
but I had a dream and I am now telling you what I dreamt about you.
If you now doubt my dream, definitely there is no cause for you to come here.
Can somebody come out and tell me what dream you had about yourself concerning this new approach.
You are saying Happy New Year without a dream.
How come?
How do you know you are in a new beginning? How do you know?
Oh no, this is intellectual property, anyway.
You say it's a slogan.
It's not a slogan, it has to do with your life.
If you say "New Year - new beginning", you should believe it.
Your soul and spirit should believe it.
When your soul believes it, then it works for you.
It's not a slogan.
Talk to me, how do you know you are in a new beginning, a new year?
Praise the Lord.
You know that you are in a new year when you have a change in mind, change of mind, change of position.
Wanting to do things differently from how you used to do them before.
As soon as you have this feeling, you believe it, you begin to do things in that new way.
That makes you a new person, a new creature, not just a change in calendar
but change in position and change in what you believe in.
To a new thing.
Thank you!
Can we believe this is what you read?
Or is this what you believe?
I have never read it but I believe it.
You believe it?
I believe it.
Ok. Tell us those things that you have changed to start the new year.
Well basically I am business man.
Can you see where this man started from?
Sit down, sit down.
I know. I know you people.
First - money!
Well, you begin a New Year when you finally discover that everything you don't want
and you don't like - unfavourable situations - end with the year.
Ask your neighbour: "What are the unfavourable situations that have ended with the year 2016?"
Ask your neighbour.
What are those unfavourable situations you have been in that have ended with that year?
Carry over is not good.
You were fighting yesterday and you wake up. The fight continues.
"Happy New Year 2017" - the fight continues.
You have not began a new year, you are still 2016.
Every unfavourable situation you have been in, must end with the outgoing year.
Amen!!
That is how we know.
The way you were thinking yesterday, is the same way you are thinking now.
The same way you approached things yesterday is the same way you are approaching things now.
What is new then?
The same anger, pain, envy, jealousy, offense, bitterness, strife - those qualities are still there.
It's not too late now.
We are in the house of God right at beginning of the year - what a wonderful year!
This is why I call it wonderful year.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Let me tell you something. Assume this year did not start on a Sunday like last year.
You know where you were last year. You were with friends.
1st of January is a time, season to visit friends, go for tours which is opposite to where we are now.
Look at where you find yourself.
The approach you give to this year is so wonderful -
the best approach one can give is to trust and obey.
This is why we are here today and it is not too late to settle our accounts, 1st of January.
Are you ready?
Yes!!
That has to do with your heart.
Blessed are the pure in heart; they shall settle their accounts.
Tell your neighbour.
That is, you will see God, you will have a new beginning, you will have a new dream.
I want to take you back again, the revelation I have for you. Are you ready to listen now?
Just listen and write it down.
I was in a vision and the Lord gave me a dream for you.
Amen!!!
You may exclude yourself, you may include yourself
It is a matter of faith.
You can say, "Yes! This man is talking to me";
"No, this man is not talking to me".
It is a matter of choice.
The Lord revealed to me that this year will come with unique challenges, so many challenges.
Tell your people they should believe and trust;
just trust and obey.
Are you writting it?
Just trust and obey.
The Lord said, "Remember I am the Father of dreams".
He said He is the Father of dreams.
He started telling me some of the people He had given dreams:
"I am sending you to your people, give them this dream".
He said He gave a dream to Abraham,
a dream to Daniel,
a dream to Joseph,
a dream to Peter and I woke up.
When I woke up, I said what is this?
I realized that this is a voice from Heaven.
The vision continued.
Here are dreams - dream of walking with the Lord, a new dream for you.
Whether you like it or not,
This year ...
Don't just delay. Something will propel you.
The unique challenges - you will know yourself that no witch doctor can help you with those.
No fake people, spiritualist or what ever can help you.
You will know yourself, you will be convinced beyond reasonable doubt that nobody can help me.
Let me run to God.
You will run a proper run to God this year.
Ah! Ok.
There will be a force you cannot resist.
Dream of walking with the Lord - a new dream for you.
Tell your Neighbour.
Dream of walking with the Lord - a new dream for you this year, 2017.
You have not started, when you leave here you will see what will be happening in your life.
Amen!!!
By the time you leave here, you will start seeing a force you cannot resist.
You want to pray the more and fast the more. (Amen!!!!)
The more the attack, the more you pray and fast this year.
You have been serving God in the past intellectually, that is how you serve God.
That will not work this year.
You will serve God with all your heart this year. That is a new dream for you.
The more the challenges, the more your desire for God this year.
So, the challenges we are talking about are a blessing.
Tell your neighbour, "It's a blessing then".
Whatever challenges T.B. Joshua is talking about are a blessing
because the more the challenges, the more my desire for God.
It's a blessing. Let it come! I want to draw closer to God.
If that will draw me closer to God, it's a blessing.
So, now, there is no cause for fear.
Before now, when challenges came in the past, 2016, you ran about, running to spiritualist.
Running to this, running to that, spending money. Being afraid!!
Running from God, instead of running to God.
It's a good year.
I know you are asking yourself: How will it happen? How will my desire for God happen?
Because when trouble comes, you always panic!
You panic and ask yourself, "How will I get out of this trouble?"
Rejoice!!
This Year.
I don't know how it will happen.
The vision I saw for you, number ONE -
a dream of walking with the Lord, a new dream for you.
A new dream has come. Happy New Year!!
Nothing and nothing will stop you from the love of God this year.
No challenges will stop you from the love of God.
No difficult circumstances can stop you from the love of God.
No infirmity will stop you from the love of God.
The more they come, the more your desire for God, in Jesus' name.
Stand up and give thanks to God!
The aim and objective of satan is to separate you.
He uses challenges and difficult circumstances to separate you,
to bring you into sin, to confess sin. This is just the aim of satan.
But his aim has been defeated! The more they come, the more your desire.
The more the challenges, trouble, sickness, infirmity, just name those things satan can bring -
the more they come, the more your desire and determination for God.
His aim has been defeated.
Be strong; trust Him. That is the key to begin this year.
When I had this vision, I was happy!
Immediately I stood up and I said, "Lord, thank you!!"
This is what I have been praying for, this is what has been rescuing me.
This is the tactic and strategy that has been protecting me.
The more these people come, the more my desire.
The more these people attack, the more my desire and determination.
The more they hate me, speak bad about me, the more my desire and my determination.
This has been protecting me.
When satan realizes that the more he attacks you, the more your desire for God, he will leave you.
At the beginning of this year, it may be a bit rough.
But when satan realizes that he cannot separate you with challenges ...
No matter the sickness, difficult circumstances, this person will not deny God.
Look at what happened to Job. The more I afflicted this person, the more he loves Jesus.
But the moment satan realizes that when he hits, you look back ...
It's not possible to look back and answer your enemy and at the same time continue the journey.
What are you saying?
Where are you going then?
Where am I going now?
I go nowhere. That is the journey you have been walking with the Lord.
That is your journey with the Lord.
Come brother, let me give you an example of what I am talking about!
This is God. Stand here.
I don't want to use anybody for satan.
I don't want to. We are in a new year.
Satan stands here, can you see?
Here is this foolish man.
Here you. You represent T.B. Joshua and this is God where you are going towards to.
On your way to God, satan will hit you.
When he hits you, it is either with disappointment, failure, setback, sickness or with something else.
He can't just hit you without those things like nightmare.
You are just going and satan just hits you. And when he hits you, you say, "Aha".
Then you cannot see where you are going. This is where you will be concentrating.
This is where you are going. Can you see where I am going now?
That is the journey you have been embarking on.
And his interest is to cause you your position,
to overthrow you and to cause you setbacks and limitations.
You see where I am going. Instead of going straight to God.
You will not be able to run a straight race.
Now, here satan hits me whilst I, T.B. Joshua, are on the journey I have been embarking on.
I will be talking, praying to fight satan but I will not look back.
I am fighting but I continue my journey.
That is why you are here today. If this journey had not been a straight race,
you would not be here today.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You would not be here today.
Your business has not been a straight race.
Your finances have not been a straight race.
Your marriage has not been a straight race.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This is why you have to run a straight race.
The more satan hits you, the more you should speed up your spiritual walk.
A hit of satan is like you are climbing a hill with a bike.
When you are climbing a hill with a bike, you put it on a small gear so that it can move.
The more you are hit with either sickness or disease does not make you a child of satan.
You can be sick in body and yet be a child of God. Continue your race. This is what the Lord said.
A new dream of walking with the Lord. A new dream for you.
When these attacks are not coming, your dream cannot come.
It is your dream that attract the challenges.
If there is no dream, there are no challenges.
No dream, no challenges.
Dream of walking with the Lord. If there is no dream of walking with the Lord, there are no challenges.
So, you are happy concerning a new dream; but it attracts challenges.
So, my brother when challenges come, remember your dream and your goal.
Nothing can be compared with your dream and your goal.
TWO - Don't forget what I said. It was not a message, it was a vision.
That your wailing will be silenced.
The voice of trouble, difficulty, and setback shall be silenced.
Their voices shall be silenced - write it down.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This will begin to manifest from June. From January to June, you will be ready to fight.
Challenges and difficulties from now until June.
But by June, when you trust and obey; satan will know that you cannot be separated. He will leave you alone.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
All over the world. I am not talking to any particular nation. All over the world.
Those who are under the influence of my voice.
Viewers; you are under the influence of my voice. Can you write it down? It will guide you.
It's is a guide to help you throughout this year.
If you can do that, satan will soon know that you are not the type to be disturbed.
To be separated from God. He will soon know.
But satan has not yet known. He still believes that he can separate you from God.
That is why he keeps pushing you. He knows that soon you will follow him and renounce God.
Let him know that nothing can separate you from the love of God.
Tell your neighbor, "Let him know that nothing can separate you from the love of God".
Can hardship, sickness, infirmity, setback, poverty, humiliation or temptation? Nothing !
Talk to your God, talk to your God right now.
Nothing can make me look back ! Nothing can separate me !
They will come with their humiliation, challenges, setback, disease and sickness!
They will come, let them come!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Dream of walking with the Lord. That means there will be grace for you, inner grace. Oh my God ...
All you lack and all you want - your business is not going well, your health is not ok.
Who owns your health? Who owns your business?
Don't you know that God is richer than your dream?
He will put everything in place.
I will not use the word "congratulations". I will say, "At last - a new dream has come".
Amen!!
You may be seated.
So, you are blessed.
Do you have any questions before we go further?
It's not really a question. You have just been speaking about me.
For 5 years and 7 months I have been in the bush fighting to come here.
I saw God, I saw Him.
You cannot see God; you can only hear His instruction.
God has given us discretion He cannot temper with. He gives us discretion to speak our mind.
But there can be a wrong discretion. We need to be in a proper state to act with God.
If you are not in a proper state to act with God, you need someone to intervene to be an intermediary.
How many years did you say you spent in the mountain?
5 years and 7 months.
Oh my God, I need to see you, Sir. Something is wrong somewhere.
While you were in the mountain, were you eating?
I was drinking once and eating once. These were the instructions.
Eating once?
I was eating once since 2002.
What time?
The 20th hour.
Ok, I want to see my brother like I said.
God is so much concerned about us, most especially when you have a family.
He will not now carry you from your family and put you on the mountain for 5 years.
With a family at home, with a wife and children.
Our God is concerned about us. He loves us so much just like He loves all His apostles.
So, that is why I am concerned that the God you are talking about carried you to the mountain for 5 years.
The family is at home and the children are home and you are eating once. What would the family eat?
You are the breadwinner of the family. I think that something is wrong somewhere.
Things were not normal.
I did not have anywhere to stay. I used to put on a green lady trousers and a pinky lady trousers.
Don't worry, Sir. I understand that something has happened, that is what I am saying.
Everything will be alright. That is why we are here. So, thank you.
Ok, any other question? Ok, let's ask our mommy here. You have a question, Ok.
So, these challenges will only attack us but not kill us?
She is afraid of death!
Do you hear what she is asking me? Do I mean that these challenges will only attack us but not kill us?
Already you have been having challenges, even as you are standing now, you have challenges.
But those challenges have not killed you, you are still alive?
Yes!
So, why do you think of death? Do you have a convenant?
No!
I was just thinking if a challenge like sickness comes on a loved one ...
Do you mean you have not been sick before?
I have.
That's it.
Thank you!!
You have answered all my questions.
Since 2017 is a wonderful year, I love my nation Kenya.
We are having elections. I am asking that you visit me in my dream so that I know how to pray about my nation.
God bless you, Sir.
You want to take me back to what I have written down there.
Even your country is one of the countries that is inside the paper there.
I will tell you a bit of what is inside that paper.
It will be very very close,
and it will be difficult to call. I will not say more than that.
Can you see? When something is close like this, it will be very difficult to call.
I don't want to go back to what is in the paper because it is one of the things in the paper.
It will be very close like this. The opposition and the ruling. It will very very difficult to call.
From there, I will not be able to say more than that because I am not here for that now.
Therefore, what can you expect from there. I will see you. Thank you.
So you love your nation so much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service